Hey, you guys? What are you doing tomorrow night?
嘿，你們明天晚上有事嗎？
Oh, well, let me see. I believe I'm..
嗯，讓我看看，我想我…
Yes, falling asleep in front of the TV.
是的，會在電視機前面睡著
Well, my agent hooked me up with six tickets to a great play.
我經紀人給我六張票 去看一出很棒的舞台劇
I could fall asleep at a play.
我也可以在那出舞台劇演出時睡覺
- What is it? - It's a one-woman play called:
-是什麼樣的舞台劇？ -是一個女人的獨場戲叫做…
Why Don't You Like Me? A Bitter Woman's Journey Through Life.
《你為什麼不喜歡我？ 一個悲慘女人的生命歷程》
- That sounds interesting. - That does sound interesting.
-聽起來挺有趣的 -是聽起來挺有趣的
To listen to a woman complain for two hours. I don't think it gets bet..
聽一個女人抱怨兩個小時 我不認為那會更…
I know! I know. We can drive. We can vote. We can work.
我知道，我們可以開車 可以投票，可以工作
What more do these broads want?
那些女人還想要什麼呢？
Well, you guys will have a great time. I promise.
你們會喜歡的，我保證
What? How come you don't have to go?
什麼？為什麼你不去呢？
I wish I could, but I found out..
我希望我可以，但是我發現…
that I have to be at work really early the next day, so I can't go.
我隔天要很早就起來工作 所以我不能去
But take the extra ticket and invite whoever you want.
但是你們可以用剩下的那張票 邀請任何人去都可以
Let's see. Who do I hate?
讓我瞧瞧我最恨誰呢？
Oh, sorry.
對不起
- Oops, sorry. - Okay.
-哦，對不起 -好的
- Okay. - Okay. Up we go.
-好的 -好的，抬起來
- Oh, gosh, okay! - All right.
-天啊，好的！ -好了
Can I ask you a question?
我可以問你一個問題嗎？
Do you think it's possible for two friends to fool around..
你覺得有沒有可能兩個朋友…
and not have it be a big deal?
打情罵俏後不會有事情發生？
No, I don't think that ever works. Why?
不可能，為什麼？
- No reason. - No, no. Rachel?
-沒事 -等一等，瑞秋？
- Who do you want to fool around with? - Nobody! Forget it.
-你想要跟誰打情罵俏呢？ -沒有人！別想太多
Joey?
喬伊嗎？
Maybe.
或許吧
- You can't. - Why?
-不行 -為什麼？
Because!
因為！
Okay, seriously, did not understand a word you just said.
說真的，你說什麼 我一點都不瞭解
- In the hall. - Okay.
-到外面去 -好
- You wanna fool around with Joey? - Yeah.
-你想要跟喬伊打情罵俏？ -是啊
Ever since I had that dream about him, I can't get it out of my head.
自從我做過那個夢之後 我就一直忘不了
I mean, what's the big deal? People do it all the time.
我是說那又會怎樣？ 很多人都是那樣做的
Who do you know that are friends that just fool around?
你認識誰只在打情罵俏的？
Okay. Off the top of my head.. Don and Janet.
好的，隨便想想… 唐跟珍娜
- Who are they? - I know them from work.
-他們是誰？ -工作上認識的人
- Both of them? - No, just one of them.
-兩個都是嗎？ -不，只有其中一個
Which one?
哪一個？
I don't know. What were the names I just said?
我不知道，我剛才說了哪些名字呢？
No, Rachel, things could get incredibly complicated.
瑞秋，事情會變得很複雜的
All right. You're right. I won't do anything with Joey. I just thought it..
好吧，你說的對，我不會對喬伊怎樣的 我只是以為…
Okay, so that's two cups of tarragon, one pound of baking soda and a red onion?
好的，那就兩杯的龍蒿、一磅的蘇打粉 還有紅洋蔥
What the hell are you cooking?
你是想要煮什麼呢？
The One With The Soap Opera Party
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
You guys won't believe what I have to do for work today.
你們不會相信 我今天要做什麼樣的工作
Yes, but, Ross, you chose a career of talking about dinosaurs.
但是羅斯，是你自己選擇 要談論恐龍的工作的
There are these two professors who are joining my department..
有兩個教授要加入我的部門
and I have to meet them here and show them around campus.
而我要在這裡跟他們碰面 然後帶他們到校園看看
What's so bad about that?
那怎麼會糟糕呢？
I just know they'll be a couple of old windbags..
我只知道他們會是那種老蓋仙
wearing tweed jackets with suede elbow patches.
穿著在手肘的地方 縫上仿麂皮的花呢外套
Ross?
羅斯？
What? These aren't suede.
怎樣？這些不是仿麂皮
Excuse me. I'm looking for someone.
不好意思，我在找人
You don't, by any chance, know a Ross Geller?
你認不認識 一個叫做羅斯蓋勒的？
No.
不認識
Hi. Hi, I'm Ross Geller.
嗨，我是羅斯蓋勒
Oh, hi. I'm Professor Wheeler.
嗨，我是魏勒教授
Oh, that's.. That's.. That's nice.
喔，這…這太好了
It's good to meet you.
很高興見到你
Thank you so much for taking the time to show me around.
謝謝你願意花時間幫我介紹環境
No, it's no big deal.
不，這一點也不麻煩的
If I weren't doing this, I'd just, you know, be at the gym working out.
如果我沒有這樣做，反正我也只是 在健身房健身而已
Is he gonna introduce us?
他會介紹我們嗎？
I think we're just blurry shapes to him now.
我想他現在跟本就看不到我們
By the way, I really enjoyed your paper..
對了，我真的很喜歡你寫的…
on the connection between geographic isolation and rapid mutagenesis.
地域隔絕與快速突變之關係的論文
I wrote that in one night.
我一個晚上就寫完了
Twenty bucks says they're married within the month.
我賭二十塊錢 他們一個月內就會結婚
Well, we should probably get going.
那麼我們最好走吧
You know, we've got a lot of ground to cover.
我們有很多地方要去
Isn't another professor supposed to come with us?
不是有另外一位教授要加入我們嗎？
I don't think so.
我想應該沒有
I'm pretty sure. A Professor Spafford from Cornell?
我非常確定 是從康乃爾來的史伯夫教授
Well, he's obviously late, and the rule in my class is:
他可能是遲到了 而我上課的規矩就是：
If you can't come on time, then don't come at all.
如果你不能準時到，那就乾脆不要到
An option that many of my students use.
我很多學生 最後都選擇後者
- Shall we? - We shouldn't wait for him?
-我們要走了嗎？ -我們不用等他嗎？
You know what, he's a big boy. I'm sure he'll find us, okay?
你知道嗎？他是個大男孩了 我確定他可以找到我們的，好嗎？
- Professor Geller? - Oh, damn it!
-蓋勒教授嗎？ -喔，媽的！
Hi, Joey, it's Jan Rogers. Can 't wait for your party tonight.
嗨，喬伊，我是珍羅傑 等不及要參加你今晚的派對了
Listen, I forgot your address. Can you give me a call? Thanks. Bye.
我忘記你的地址了，可以回電給我嗎？ 謝謝，拜
-Hi. -Hi.
-嗨 -嗨
What's happening?
怎麼了？
It's a real shame you can't make it to that one-woman show tonight.
真可惜你沒有辦法參加 今晚的女人獨角戲
I'd love to, but I gotta get up so early the next day.
我也想去，但是我隔天要好早起來
- You know me, work comes first. - Oh, yeah, yeah.
-你知道我的，工作最重要 -是啊，是啊
Hi, Joey, it's Jan Rogers. Can 't wait for your party tonight.
嗨，喬伊，我是珍羅傑 等不及參加你今晚的派對了
Stupid Jan Rogers!
珍羅傑，你還真蠢！
You are having a party tonight?
你今晚要開派對？
- No. - Joey!
-沒有 -喬伊！
Yeah.
是的
I'm kind of having a thing for the Days of Our Lives people.
我幫《我們的日子》的人員 辦了一個聚會
And you weren't gonna tell us?
而你卻不告訴我們？
How did you think you were gonna get away with that?
你認為你可以逃得掉嗎？
I do it every year.
我每年都這樣做啊
You do that every year?!
你每年都這樣做！
I didn't have to tell you that!
我不需要告訴你的！
God, I'm stupider than Jan Rogers!
天啊，我比珍羅傑還愚蠢！
That's why you got us tickets to that play, to get rid of us!
所以你就給我們去看舞台劇的票 甩掉我們！
Yeah.
是啊
Last year is that why you sent us to that Medieval Times restaurant?
去年你就送我們去那間中古世紀餐廳？
Yeah.
是啊
And the year before that, you set up that nighttime tour of that button factory?
而前年你幫我們安排鈕扣工廠之旅？
I can't believe you guys went for that one.
我不敢相信那個你們也會去
Why wouldn't you invite us to your parties?
你為什麼不邀請我們參加你的派對呢？
You're fine, okay? But everyone else acts like an idiot around famous people.
你還好，但是其他人在名人面前 都表現的像傻瓜一樣
Well, then, so just invite me.
那麼，就只邀請我就好了啊
Please, I was trying to be nice. You're the worst one.
拜託，我只是在說好聽話 你是最糟糕的
Joey, come on! Please, please? Let me come. I will behave. I promise.
喬伊，別這樣！拜託啦 讓我參加，我會克制自己，我保證
- I will behave. Please, please, please. - Okay, fine. You can come.
-我會克制自己，拜託 -好啦，你可以參加
But don't tell anybody else. It's up on the roof at 8.
但是不要告訴其他人 八點鐘在屋頂上面
A soap-opera roof party?!
肥皂劇屋頂派對！
I'm going to a soap-opera roof party! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
我要參加肥皂劇屋頂派對！ 喔，我的天啊！…
And it's out of my system.
好了，發洩完了
And then my wife and I went on a cruise to the Galapagos.
然後我老婆跟我搭游輪到加拉巴哥
There was a seafood buffet you wouldn't believe.
你們不會相信他們的 隨你吃海鮮餐廳有多棒
There were clams and mussels and oysters..
有蛤蜊、河蚌還有生蠔
and cracked crab..
還有螃蟹…
and snow crab..
還有花蟹…
and king crab.
還有帝王蟹
It's a pity I'm allergic to shellfish.
真可惜我對帶殼類海鮮對敏
So where did you get your undergraduate degree?
你大學是在哪念的呢？
- And that's not all I'm allergic to. - Oh, it's not over.
-而且我不只對那些過敏 -喔，還沒有結束啊
I'm also allergic to peanuts and cashews..
我還有對花生跟腰果過敏
and almonds and filberts..
還有杏仁果跟榛果…
So basically all nuts!
所以基本上是所有的堅果類！
Interestingly, no.
有趣的是，並不盡然
You're kind of playing it fast and loose with the word "interesting."
你在說「有趣的是」時說的挺慢的 讓人以為就是如此
If you'll excuse me, I'm going to use the restroom.
不好意思失陪一下，我要去洗手間
When I come back, remind me to tell you..
當我回來的時候，提醒我告訴你們…
about the different types of animal dander I'm allergic to.
我對哪些動物過敏
Oh, my God!
喔，我的天啊！
I've lost the will to live.
我已經喪失活下去的意志力了
- Let's ditch him. - What?
-我們甩了他 -什麼？
While he's still in the bathroom. I am begging you.
在他還在洗手間的時候，我求求你
Okay. Okay, fine, but I just have one question for you.
好的，但是我有個問題要先問你
When we exit, should we walk or run..
我們出去的時候 應該是用走的、跑的…
or prance or stroll..?
跳的還是散步出去？
Stop it! Stop it! He talks slow, but he might pee fast. Okay, let's move!
別說了！他的話說得慢 搞不好尿得快，我們快走！
- We actually managed to salvage the day. - Yeah, we did.
-幸好今天過的還不錯 -是的，沒錯
Thanks for spending so much time with me.
謝謝你花這麼多時間陪我
I'm so lucky it worked out you don't have class on Tuesday.
我很幸運，你星期二沒有課
Right.
沒錯
Oh, hey, you guys, this is Charlie.
你們好，這位是查莉
Charlie, this is Phoebe and my sister, Monica.
查莉，這是菲比，還有我妹妹摩妮卡
- Hi. - Charlie will be joining my department.
-嗨 -查莉將要加入我們繫上
- You're a paleontologist too? - Yeah.
-你也是古生物學家嗎？ -是的
Oh, okay. Now, what do you think..
那好，你對於…
of Renyard's new theory of species variegation in segmented arthropods?
雷諾的分割類人猿物種多樣性的新理論 有何評價？
Well, I think he's a little out there, but he does have some interesting ideas.
我覺得他有點太前衛了 但是他是有些有趣的觀點
Oh, I'm sorry. I have to take this. Excuse me.
很抱歉，我要接一下電話 不好意思
Renyard's theory of species variegation?
雷諾的物種多樣性？
I saw the article on your coffee table. I memorized the title to freak you out.
我在你的咖啡桌上看到一篇文章 我背下了標題想要來嚇你
So did you two have fun?
你們倆個相處的愉快嗎？
Oh, my God. She's great.
天啊，她真的是太棒了
We have so much in common, and she's just cool, you know? And funny.
我們有許多共同點，她真是太酷了 你知道嗎？還很風趣
And I don't know if you've noticed, but she's a hottie!
而且我不知道你有沒有注意到 但是她真辣！
Hi!
嗨！
Hi, you guys. Listen, you know what, I'm not feeling really well..
嗨，大家聽著 我覺得不太舒服…
and I don't think I'm gonna get to go to the play.
我想我可能不能去看舞台劇表演了
Really? What's wrong?
真的嗎？怎麼了？
I don't know. I think it's kind of serious.
我不知道，好像蠻嚴重的
You know, I was watching this thing on TV this morning..
我今天早上在電視上有看到…
about Newcastle disease, and I think I might have it.
什麼關於新堡疾病的 我想我可能感染到了
Newcastle disease is a secretion-borne virus..
新堡疾病是跟分泌物有關的病毒
that only affects chickens and other poultry.
只有雞或是其它家禽才會被傳染到
Okay, who's this?
好的，這是誰呢？
I'm sorry. Rachel, this is Charlie Wheeler. She's a colleague.
抱歉，瑞秋，這位是查莉魏勒 她是我同事
Hi. Well, I would shake your hand..
嗨，我應該要跟你握手的…
but I'm sure you don't want to get my chicken disease.
但是我想你不會想要 被傳染到我的雞病
- Rachel, can I see you for a second? - Sure.
-瑞秋，我可以跟你談一下嗎？ -當然
You're not sick.
你沒有生病
What? Yes, I am!
什麼？我當然有！
Okay, then why are you all dressed up?
那麼為什麼你要穿成這樣呢？
When you're sick, you do whatever you can to make yourself feel better.
當你生病的時候，你會做任何事情 來讓自己覺得好過一些
You just want to stay home so you can make a move on Joey.
你只是想要待在家裡 對喬伊採取行動
No, I heard you before. That is so not what this is.
不是，我聽進去了你之前說的話 事情不是這樣的
Okay, then what is this?
好的，那是怎麼回事呢？
Okay.
好的
Joey is having a secret Days of Our Lives party up on the roof.
喬伊幫《我們的日子》在屋頂舉行 秘密派對
And he sent you guys to the play to get rid of you.
他送你們去看舞台劇來甩掉你們
What?!
什麼？
What? What's going on?
什麼？這是怎麼回事？
Joey is having a secret Days of Our Lives party up on the roof!
喬伊幫《我們的日子》 在屋頂舉行秘密派對
He didn't want you to know about it, but I came over here to tell you.
他不想要讓你們知道 但是我還是過來告訴你們了
- You came to say you were sick. - All right, professor or detective?
-你是過來說你生病的 -你到底是教授還是偵探？
Wait, Joey's having a party, and he wasn't gonna invite us?
等等，喬伊要開派對 但不邀請我們？
He does it every year. That's why he's sending you to the play.
他每年都那樣做的 這就是為什麼他要請我們去看舞台劇
That's why he sent us to that medieval restaurant and to that button factory.
這就是為什麼他請我們去中古世紀餐廳 還有鈕扣工廠
And that horrible museum tour?
而有那次糟糕的博物館之旅嗎？
No, I arranged that.
不是，那是我安排的
Hey, you guys, I'm turning in. Have fun.
你們好，我過來打招呼 祝你們玩的愉快
We know about your party, Joey.
我們知道你的派對了，喬伊
- What party? - The game's over. Take off your robe.
-什麼派對？ -遊戲結束了，把睡袍脫掉吧
Okay, I mean..
好的，我是說…
Close it up! Close it up!
穿起來！穿起來！
Nice to meet you.
很高興見到你
Hey, you made it! All right!
嘿，你來了！太好了！
Glad you could make it. Thanks for coming.
很高興你來了，謝謝你參加
- Oh, my God. Kyle Lowder! - Hi.
-我的天啊，凱爾羅德！ -嗨
I love you!
我愛你！
Hey. That's why I didn't invite you. You have to calm down, all right?
喂，這就是我為什麼不想邀請你 你要冷靜點，好嗎？
Just go get yourself a drink or something.
去喝點飲料什麼的
Oh, yeah, that's what you want. My inhibitions lowered.
是啊，你就是要讓我的自制力潰堤
Oh, my God, can you believe we're surrounded by all this?
我的天啊，你敢相信我們 被這些人包圍著嗎？
I can barely control myself.
我幾乎控制不了自己
Monica, you might want to remember that you're married.
摩妮卡，你該瞭解到你已經結婚了
Where is Chandler anyway?
錢德呢？
Oh, my God! Chandler!
我的天啊！錢德！
Where the hell is everybody?
大家死哪去了？
Why Don't You Like Me?
你為什麼不喜歡我？
Chapter 1: My First Period.
第一章：我的第一次生理期
Hey, Joey said no autographs.
喬伊說不能要簽名的
But if she's getting one, I want one too!
但是如果她有，那我也要！
"To Monica." And none of this "best wishes" crap. I want "love."
「給摩妮卡」，而且別寫什麼 「祝福」之類的，要寫「愛」
Okay, actually, Mon, Matthew was giving me his phone number.
事實上，摩妮卡 馬修只是給我他的電話
Oh, man! If I had known I was coming to this party..
天啊！如果我知道 我要參加這個派對…
I never would've gotten married!
我就一定不會結婚！
- It was nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
-很高興認識你 -很高興認識你
- Call me. - We will!
-打電話給我 -我們會的！
Look at you with all the guys! I guess you've forgotten all about Joey.
瞧瞧你周旋在眾多男生之間！ 我猜你把喬伊都忘光了
Yeah, well, I guess I have forgotten about Joey.
是的，我想我是忘了喬伊
And clearly, you've forgotten about Chandler.
而很明顯地，你也忘了錢德
Please. Chandler's the love of my life.
拜託，錢德是我的摯愛
Oh, leather pants! Have mercy!
皮褲耶！不會吧！
So do you get to go to things like this often?
你常常參加這種派對嗎？
Come on, this is New York.
是啊，這裡是紐約耶
I mean, one night you're at a rooftop party filled with soap stars..
我是說，有時候晚上在屋頂上 跟很多肥皂劇明星開派對…
and the next night, you're..
有時候，就是…
Who am I kidding, this is so cool.
我是在騙誰呢，這實在太酷了！
So it's probably gonna be hard for you to leave Boston, huh?
離開波士頓對你而言 一定很困難吧？
Actually, I'm kind of happy to be leaving. I just broke up with someone.
事實上我很高興離開那 我剛剛分手
Oh, so sad.
真令人傷心
Still, it can't be easy for you to leave Harvard.
但是離開哈佛 一定也是不容易
Especially after working with a Nobel Prize winner like Albert Wintermeyer.
尤其是跟諾貝爾得主 亞伯特溫麥爾共事過
Actually, Albie is the guy I broke up with.
事實上，阿亞就是我分手的人
- You dated Albert Wintermeyer? - Yeah.
-你跟亞伯特溫麥爾交往過？ -是的
And you called him "Albie"?
而你叫他「阿亞」？
I mean, that's like calling Albert Einstein..
我是說，這就像是叫 亞伯特愛因斯坦…
Albie.
阿亞一樣
Yeah, well, he is a brilliant man.
對，他是個很聰明的男人
You think? I mean, you dated the guy..
你認為嗎？我是說，你跟一個…
who improved the accuracy of radiocarbon dating by a factor of 10!
提升了碳十四的精準測定法的 男人交往！
Yes, and while that is everything one looks for in a boyfriend..
是的，而那正是每個人 對男朋友的需求
he had a lot of issues.
他有很多問題
Oh, like what?
像是什麼呢？
I'm sorry. I don't mean to pry. It's just that this must be..
很抱歉，我不是要刺探隱私 只是跟…
what regular people experience when they watch Access Hollywood.
一般人看《娛樂新聞》 有一樣的反應
Okay, you want the dirt?
好的，你想要知道內幕嗎？
Albie was seriously insecure.
阿亞有很嚴重的沒安全感
He was really intimidated by the guy I dated before him.
他對我之前男朋友感到非常地不安
Who's intimidating to a guy who won the Nobel Prize?
誰能夠威脅到諾貝爾獎得主呢？
A guy who won two.
得過兩次諾貝爾獎的人
Two? What..?
兩次？什麼？
Don't tell me you dated Benjamin Hobart?
別告訴我你跟班傑明赫伯交往過？
Yeah, for three years.
是的，交往了三年
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
Have you ever been in a relationship with someone who hasn't won the Nobel Prize?
你有沒有跟沒得過 諾貝爾獎的人交往過呢？
No.
沒有
But there was my first boyfriend, Billy.
但我的第一個男朋友比利沒有
Oh, yeah? No Nobel Prizes for him?
是嗎？他沒有得諾貝爾嗎？
No, but he did just win the MacArthur "genius grant."
沒有，但是他倒是得過麥克阿瑟的 「天才獎學金」
What a loser.
真是個窩囊廢
Some more wine?
要再喝點酒嗎？
Hey, Ross. How's it going with Charlie?
羅斯，跟查莉進行的如何呢？
Oh, great. After I finish my wine..
很好，在我喝完酒之後…
I'm gonna blow my average-sized brains out.
我正常的腦袋會爆炸
What's the matter?
怎麼了？
She only dates geniuses and Nobel Prize winners.
她只跟天才還有諾貝爾獎得主交往
Oh, my God, at the Chinese restaurant earlier today..
我的天啊，今天稍早在中國餐廳…
I put chopsticks in my mouth and pretended to be a woolly mammoth.
我把筷子放在嘴中假裝是長毛象
I always loved that.
我很喜歡那樣耶
Of course you would! Your brains are smaller than mine!
當然你會喜歡，你的大腦比我的小！
I can't compete with the guys she goes out with.
我不能跟她交往過的男人相比
They're so out of my league.
他們比我好太多了
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
- Worse? - Oh, much, much worse.
-還有更糟的嗎？ -比那還糟
I did my impression of Joan Rivers as one of the earliest amphibians.
我還模仿瓊瑞薇演出最早的兩棲人
"Can we walk?"
「我們可以去散步嗎？」
- Oh, you like that? - No.
-你喜歡嗎？ -不
What?
怎樣？
Come on! I think that's funny!
別這樣！我覺得這樣很好笑啊！
Woolly mammoth.
長毛象
It's good!
很好笑耶！
I bet you're thinking that now would be a great time for an intermission, huh?
我想你們一定在想現在該中場休息了 是嗎？
Oh, yes. God, yes.
是的，上帝，拜託
Well, you're not gonna get one!
你們不會休息的！
Because in life, there are no intermissions, people!
因為現實生活是沒有中場休息的！
Now, Chapter 7: Divorce is a Four-Letter Word!
現在開始第七章：離婚是四個字母！
How could he leave me?!
他怎麼可以離開我呢？
I don't know. You seem lovely.
我不知道，你看起來挺可愛的
Ross, this is one of my costars, Dirk. Dirk, this is my good friend Ross.
羅斯，這是我同事登克 登克，這是我好朋友羅斯
- Nice to meet you. - So, what show are you on?
-很高興認識你 -你是哪出戲的呢？
I'm not an actor. I'm a professor of paleontology.
我不是演員，我是古生物學教授
That's science.
科學的東東
Hey, well, listen, I play a scientist on Days.
嘿，聽著，我在 《我們的日子》裡面演的是科學家
Yeah, my character just won a Nobel Prize.
我的角色剛剛贏得諾貝爾獎
Ross, Dirk was wondering about the woman you brought and if you guys are together?
羅斯，登克想問你帶來的那個女生 是不是你的女朋友
Well, no, but..
嗯，不是，不過…
I mean, she only goes out with really, really smart guys.
她只跟非常、非常聰明的男生交往
Hey, I got a 690 on my SATs.
嘿，我大學入學考考了六百九十分
I'd lead with that.
真是高分啊
That's it. Just sign right on the bra.
好了，就簽在胸罩上面就可以了
Monica!
摩妮卡！
Don't worry, Joe. I won't come next year!
別擔心喬伊，我明年不會來了！
What the..?
是怎樣？
What do you got there?
你那是什麼呢？
Just some boys gave me their phone numbers.
只是一些男生給我的電話
Oh, really? Let me see.
真的嗎？讓我看看
Damn, that's a lot of guys.
該死，還真多男生呢
Are you a little slutty?
你是不是有點騷呢？
I think I am.
沒錯
Let me see if I approve of any of these clowns.
讓我看看有哪些小丑是夠格的
- This guy wears a rug. - Well..
-這個男的戴假髮 -喔…
This guy's Canadian.
這個男的是加拿大人
Oh, and this guy is in a cult, okay?
這個男的參加秘密教派
It'll cost you $5000 to get to level three, and I don't feel any different.
你得花五千塊才能升到第三級 但我也沒有感到有什麼不同
Pass. Pa.. Oh, pass. Pass.
跳過，哈…喔，跳過，跳過
- Why? What's wrong with these guys? - Well, nothing major.
-為什麼？這些男生有什麼不好的？ -嗯，沒有什麼特別不好的
It's just that, you know, they're not really good enough for you..
只是他們全都配不上你
and you deserve the best.
而你應該跟最好的人在一起
Joey, you're so sweet.
喬伊，你真是貼心
It's true, but it doesn't matter. I already know who you're going home with.
那倒是，不過沒關係 我已經知道你會跟誰回家了
Who?
誰？
Me.
我
What?
什麼？
Really?
真的？
Yeah, because we live together. It's a joke! It's a joke.
是啊，因為我們住在一起 開玩笑的！開玩笑的
Right! That's funny! I get it!
是啊，真好笑！我聽懂了
- Got you! - You're funny, Joey.
-唬到你了！ -你真好笑，喬伊
Oh, my God.
喔，我的天
So how did you enjoy the play?
喜歡那場舞台劇表演嗎？
Oh, my God. Honey, I am so, so, so, so sorry.
我的天，親愛的，我真是抱歉
Well, you should be.
沒錯
You missed the most powerful three hours in the history of the theater.
你錯失了戲劇史上最強勁的三個小時
- You really liked it? - Oh, yeah. I mean, at first I hated it.
-你真的喜歡嗎？ -對，一開始我是很討厭的
But why wouldn't l? Because as a man, I've been trained not to listen!
我一定會的啊，因為身為男人 我就是被訓練成不要聆聽的！
But after Chapter 16:
但是在第十六章之後
Fat, Single and Ready to Mingle..
《肥胖、單身而且準備好要亂搞》
I was uplifted.
我就被鼓舞起來了
- Oh, really? - Oh, yeah.
-真的嗎？ -是的
I had no idea the amazing journey you go through as a woman.
我根本不曉得 女人的經歷過程是這樣的神奇
Tell me.. Tell me about your first period.
告訴我，跟我說你的第一次生理期
No!
不！
Did somebody sign your bra?
有人在你的胸罩上簽名嗎？
So I got it when I was 13. Very difficult.
我是十三歲時候來的，非常難過
Hey, Ross? So listen, about you and the dinosaur girl?
羅斯，聽著 關於你跟那個恐龍女生的事
Are you really just gonna let a couple of Nobel Prizes scare you off?
你真的就要讓幾個諾貝爾獎 把你嚇走嗎？
What is that? Come on, a piece of paper?
那是怎樣？不過是幾張論文不是嗎？
It's actually a million-dollar prize.
事實上是一百萬的獎金
Go, Charlie!
查莉你真行！
But my point is..
但是我的重點是…
okay, so she dated them, but she also broke up with them.
她是跟他們交往過，不過都分手了啊
Maybe she's looking to, you know, slum it with some average Joe Ph.D.
或許她正在尋找一般平凡的博士而已
Yeah, maybe, and I do have my whole career in front of me.
或許吧，而我的事業正在發展中
I mean..
我是說…
I could still win a Nobel Prize.
我還是有可能贏得諾貝爾獎的
Although the last two papers I've written were widely discredited.
雖然我上兩份論文被廣泛地批評過
You're so much more than just brains. You are sweet and kind and funny.
你不只是聰明而已 你很貼心、很仁慈又很風趣
And sexy.
還有性感
Okay, well, give her a chance to see all that.
好的，給她一個機會見識這全部
Yeah. Yeah. You're right.
對，你說的沒錯
- Thanks. I'm gonna go find her. - Good for you.
-謝謝，我要去找她了 -太好了
And your paper on punctuated equilibrium in the Devonian Era was topnotch.
還有你關於泥盆紀時期突顯均勢的論文 是有很精闢見解的
Stop going through my stuff!
不要再翻我的東西了！
I just wanted to let you know I've changed my mind.
我只想讓你知道，我改變主意了
I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna kiss Joey.
我要做了，我要去親喬伊
No! You can't! Friends hooking up is a bad idea.
不！你不行！朋友在一起是件壞事
Please! What about you and Chandler?
拜託！那你跟錢德呢？
That's different. I was drunk and stupid.
那是不一樣的，我喝醉了而且很蠢
Well, hello?
那你在說什麼啊？
What about all the guys that you got the phone numbers from?
那些給你電話的男生呢？
- Why don't you just kiss one of them. - I could..
-你為什麼不去親其中一個 -我是可以…
but I don't want to. I want to kiss Joey.
但是我不想，我想要親喬伊
All right. I think it's a big mistake, but it's your decision.
好吧，我認為這樣是不對的 但那是你自己的決定
I'm gonna do it.
我要去做了
- And I can't stop you? - No.
-而我無法阻止你嗎？ -對
Well, can I at least have the phone numbers.
那至少把那些電話號碼給我吧
Hey, Rach, have you seen Charlie anywhere?
瑞秋，你有看到查莉嗎？
I'm smarter than him!
我比他聰明多了！
Hey, thank you so much for these tickets, Chandler.
謝謝你送我們票，錢德
This was a really important experience for me and I wanted to share it with you.
這對我是很重要的經歷 而我想跟你們分享
You're so wonderful.
你真是好人
Why Don't You Like Me?
你為什麼不喜歡我？
Chapter 1: My First Period.
第一章：我的第一次生理期
I can't believe you guys bought that. Enjoy your slow death.
我不敢相信你們竟然這麼好騙 慢慢享受死刑吧